Andrew Ellicott Douglass papers, 1867-1962
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Tree-Ring Materials, 1894-1966
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1943-1944 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Lectures & Addresses: "Notes on Research," (Sigma Xi, Methodist Church, Tucson, AZ). May 5, 1944 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1944-1947 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Lectures & Addresses: "Notes on Past Presidents," (Faculty Meeting honoring President Alfred Atkinson, University of Arizona). May 10, 1947 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1947-1949 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Lectures & Addresses: "How Tree Rings Date Prehistoric Ruins," (Heard Museum, Phoenix, AZ). March 24-25, 1949 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1949-1950 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1950-1951 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1951-1952 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Lectures & Addresses (itemized list in folder). 1952-1959 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Lectures & Addresses: Wide Wide World TV program (NBC, notes and drafts). November 24, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Lectures & Addresses: Wide Wide World TV program (script, correspondence). (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Series V: Personal Material (Part II), 1867-1965
  - Organizations
    - Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia. 1936-1937 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - American Alpine Club. 1905-1911 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science. 1904-1957 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Pacific Division. 1914-1919 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Professors. 1917, 1925-1947 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - American Astronomical Society (correspondence). 1914-1952 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - American Astronomical Society (programs). 1914-1959 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - American Forestry Association. 1923-1954 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - American Geographical Society. 1915-1943 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - American Geophysical Union. 1930-1952 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - American Geophysical Union (membership lists). (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - American Geophysical Union (programs). 1930-1958 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - American Meteorological Society. 1920-1929 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - American Meteorological Society. 1930-1959 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - American Museum of Natural History. 1919-1926 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - American Philosophical Society. 1941-1958 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Astronomical and Astrophysical Society of America. 1910-1915 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Astronomical Society of the Pacific. 1916-1958 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Boy Scouts of America. 1916-1949 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Ecological Society of America. 1920-1922 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Harvard Club (including correspondence with Rev. J. Rockwood Jenkins). 1915-1958 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - National Economic League. 1917-1932 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - National Geographic Society. 1905-1958 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Phi Beta Kappa. 1915-1958 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Phi Kappa Phi. 1919-1958 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Royal Astronomical Society. 1899-1943 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Save the Redwoods League. 1920-1955 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Science League of America. 1925-1926 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Sigma Xi. 1925-1955 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Social Clubs (Non-Arizona). 1898-1938 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Society of American Foresters. 1914-1917, 1942 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Sons of the American Revolution. 1907-1935 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Union Geographique Internationale. 1929-1948 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Y.M.C.A. 1914-1939 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - American Folk-lore Society (Arizona Branch). 1906, 1917 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Arizona Archaeological and Historical Society. 1916-1954 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Arizona Education Association. 1916-1939 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Arizona Pioneers' Historical Society. 1931-1957 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Artcraft Society of Tucson. 1907-1910 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Grace Episcopal Church, Tucson. 1911-1932 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Heard Museum, Phoenix, AZ. 1948-1955 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Hohokam Museum Association. 1937-1949 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Kino Memorial Association, Tucson, AZ. 1931-1936 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Museum of Northern Arizona, Flagstaff. 1930-1958 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Old Pueblo Club, Tucson, AZ. 1907-1936 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Tucson Chautauqua Association. 1919-1921 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Tucson Luncheon Club. 1915-1920 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Tucson Natural History Society. 1925-1938 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Masonic Groups: Freemasons (general correspondence). 1906-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Masonic Groups: Freemasons (program). (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Masonic Groups: Freemasons (miscellaneous material). (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Masonic Groups: Freemasons (Flagstaff, AZ, Lodge no.7). 1902-1954 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Masonic Groups: Order of the Eastern Star. 1905-1926 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Masonic Groups: Royal Arch Masons (Tucson chapter no.3). 1906-1928 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Masonic Groups: A.E.D.'s Masonic aprons and medals. (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Rotary Club, Tucson (miscellaneous material). (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Rotary Club, Tucson (correspondence). 1921-1957 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Rotary Club, Tucson ( Tucsotarian). 1929-1958 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Rotary Clubs in other cities (miscellaneous publications). (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Tucson Chamber of Commerce (A.E.D.'s membership). (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Tucson Chamber of Commerce (general papers). 1911-1949 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Tucson Lead Crosses (correspondence & clippings). 1924-1925 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Tucson Lead Crosses (various notes). (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Tucson Lead Crosses (photographs). (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Tucson Lead Crosses (tracings and transcriptions). (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence
    - Family: Sarah Elizabeth (Hale) Douglass. 1907-1912 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Family: Mary Caroline Douglass. 1907-1936 (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
    - Family: Malcolm Douglass, Jr. 1907-1930 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Family: Hale Family. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Family: Thomas Hale, Jr. 1914-1953 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Family: Material regarding Kenyon College, Gambier, OH. (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Family: Material regarding Norwich University, Northfield, VT. (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Family: Sarah (Hale) Douglass's Drawing Book. (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Family: Moses H. Douglass. 1907-1951 (Box 149, Folder 1-4)
    - Family: Edith (Blydenburgh) Douglass. (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Family: Ruth (Blydenburgh) Kidder. (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Family: Mary (Douglass) Rackliffe and Edith Douglass. (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Family: Francis Malcolm Douglass. (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Family: Andrew Ellicott Douglass, II. (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Family: Curtis Family. 1905-1953 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Family: Frank K. Douglass & Family (English). 1912-1949 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Family: Lankfor Family. 19005-1943 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Family: Harry L Smith Family. 1911-1953 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Family: Wilbur-Burton Family. 1908-1931 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Family: J.C. Whittington & Family. 1907-1942 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Family: Mary R. Delacroix. 1921-1937 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Family: Walter Evans Devereux. 1938-1954 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Family: David Bates Douglas, Jr. & Family. 1914-1951 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Family: Morton Douglass (son of D.B. Douglass, Jr.). 1947-1951 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Family: Mabelle (Woodbury) Douglass. 1887, 1915, 1952 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Family: William M. Ellicott. 1932-1943 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Family: John Hunter Family. 1911-1952 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Family: Lucille (Ellicott) MacDonald. 1931-1958 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Family: Ethel (Douglass) Rickard. 1916-1954 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Family: various (mostly Evans family). (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Personal: Harold Bell Wright. 1919-1933 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Personal: James H. McClintock. 1907-1932 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Personal: William Tyler Olcott. 1929-1938 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Personal: Bishop William Scarlett. 1918-1947 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Personal: Mr. & Mrs. W.C. Roberts. 1928-1932 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Personal: Sykes Family. 1895-1962 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Personal: miscellaneous. 1906-1958 (Box 151, Folder 7-12)
    - Personal: "Edna." (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Political (general). 1911-1958 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Political (various). 1908-1947 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Political: American politics. (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Political: Education. (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Political: Foreign Affairs. (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Political: Health, Social Issues. (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Political: Religion. (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Political: Science. (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Political: Museums. (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - World War I and Europe
    - World War I: Appeals for aid and relief. (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - World War I: Arizona Council of Defense. 1917-1918 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - World War I: Articles and clippings. (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - World War I: Books on the War (A.E.D.'s notes). (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - World War I: League to Enforce Peace. 1916-1920 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - World War I: miscellaneous war material. (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - World War I: "Preparedness." (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - World War I: Red Cross. (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - World War I: U.S. Food Administration, County Apportionment Committee. 1917 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - World War I: U.S. Government Publications. (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - World War I: Post-War relief agencies. (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Europe: trip (diary, hotel receipts, menus, ships plan, etc.). Summer 1910 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Europe: trip (brochures, guides, maps). Summer 1910 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Europe: trip (diary, passport, notes, menus, hotel receipts). December 1912-January 1913 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Europe: trip (brochures, guides, maps). December 1912- January 1913 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Europe: book of mounted postcards. (Box 154)
  - Personal Material
    - Autobigraphical notes. (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographies of A.E.D.'s writings. (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Biographical information for various publications. 1909-1958 (Box 155, Folder 3-4)
    - Biographical information for the National Cyclopedia of American Biography. 1906-1935 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Biographical information for Who's Who. 1912-1945 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Notes and memos. 1909-1958 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Medical Records. (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - "Thanks for Tree-ring Dates," (formal statement of appreciation from the American Association and the Society for American Aarchaeology). December 29, 1956 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Tributes (miscellaneous). (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Death and obituary notices. (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Pesonal Miscellany. (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Photographs. (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Philosophy (personal thoughts on a number of subjects). 1896-1958 (Box 156, Folder 3-5)
    - Philosophy ("Modern Religion"). 1916-1933 (Box 156a, Folder 1)
    - Philosophy ("Scientific Approach to Religion"). 1922-1929 (Box 156a, Folder 2)
    - Addresses (mailing). (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Books, subscriptions (correpsondence). (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Books and magazines (including notes on reading). (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Calling Cards (friends, associates, business). (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Contributions to Charity. 1909-1952 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - "Crank Literature," (pseudo-science, politics, religion). (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Form letter for job application. 1914 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - "Humor" clippings. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Inventions (Observatory Apparatus). (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Inventions (Range Finder). 1900-1913 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Inventions (miscellaneous). 1895-1954 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Letters lists. 1890-1953 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - "Others' Sermons" clippings. (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Programs: music, drama, lectures (Tucson). (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Programs: music, drama, lectures (various). (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Rainbow Bridge trip. May 1927 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - "Requests for Financial Aid." 1940s and 1950s (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Stationary samples (various letter head). (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Tuberculosis (care and prevention). (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Christmas cards. (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
    - Insurance (accident and fire). (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Insurance (Life, Equitable Life Insurance Society). 1898-1919 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Insurance (Life, Massachusetts Hospital Life Insurance, Co.). 1910-1960 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Insurance (Life, various). (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - A.E.D.'s coin collection (information only). (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - A.E.D.'s arrowheads & other Indian relics (information only). (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Diaries & Notebooks (includes notes, photographs, etc). 1906-1919 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Diaries & Notebooks (for several trips). 1920-1927 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Diaries & Notebooks (notes). 1928-1930 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Diaries & Notebooks (includes "coast redwood trip"). 1931-1932 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Diaries & Notebooks. 1933-1935 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Diaries & Notebooks. 1937-1939 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Diaries & Notebooks. 1940-1942, 1945-1958 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Automobiles: Correspondence and Legal Papers. 1909-1955 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Automobiles: brochures, ads, etc. (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Automobiles: License. (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Automobiles: Insurance. (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Automobiles: Maps, Tourist Guides, etc. (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Automobiles: miscellaneous. (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Automobiles: Bills. (Box 161, Folder 7-10)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Elements of Geometry and Trigonometry, from the works of A.M. Legendre...adapted by Charles Davies. New York, A.S. Barnes, 1878 (used by A.E.D. at Punchard and Trinity). (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Preliminary Report of the Commission Appointed by the University of Pennsylvania to Investigate Modern Spiritualism, in accordance with the request of the late Henry Seybert. Philadelphia, J.B. Lippincott, 1887. (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Principles of Weatern Civilization, by Benjamin Kidd. New York, Macmillan, 1902. (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Social Revolution, by Benjamin Kidd. New York, Macmillan, 1894. (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: The Psychology of Religion, by Edwin D. Starbuck. London, W. Scott, 1900. (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Modern Astronomy, by Herbert Hall Turner. New York, Dutton, 1900. (Box 162)
    - Books Annotated by A.E.D.: Polish Acts of Atrocity Against the German Minority in Poland, second edition. Berlin-New York, 1940 (Box 162)
  - Financial Records
    - A.E.D.'s general ledger book. (Box 163)
    - Eary Ledger. 1913-1924 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Summaries for income tax. 1923-1945 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous financial notes. 1914-1953 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous business correspondence. 1907-1944 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Warrants (state of Arizona). 1933-1934 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Articles and clippings relating to business. (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Arizona Central Bank (Flagstaff). 1899, 1906-1919 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Arizona National Bank, Tucson National Bank. 1911-1923 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Bank (Flagstaff). 1906-1915 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Citizens National Bank (Los Angeles). 1911-1915, 1924 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Consolidated National Bank of Tucson. 1907-1931 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Valley National Bank (Phoenix). 1939-1953 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - New England Banks and Trust Companies. (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co.: correspondence. 1908-1945 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co.: bank statements. 1908-1953 (Box 164, Folder 2-6)
    - Arizona Central Bank (Flagstaff). 1902-1907 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Citizens Bank, Mrs. A.E.D.'s account (Flagstaff). 1907-1909 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Citizens National Bank (Los Angeles). 1905-1925 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Consolidated National Bank (Tucson). 1906-1931 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co., Mrs. A.E.D.'s account. 1908-1911 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. 1908-1923 (Box 165, Folder 6-23)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. (checks and check stubs). 1924-1934 (Box 166)
    - Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. (checks and check stubs). 1935-1953 (Box 167)
    - Deposit slips: Arizona National Bank (Tucson). 1917-1925 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Deposit slips: Consolidated National Bank (Tucson). 1925-1936 (Box 168, Folder 2-11)
    - Deposit slips: Cooperative Bank & Trust Co. (Tucson). 1924-1925 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Deposit slips: Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. (Tucson). 1907-1953 (Box 168, Folder 13-19)
    - Deposit slips: Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. (Tucson), Mrs. A.E.D.'s account. 1920, 1927-1940 (Box 169, Folder 1-2)
    - Deposit slips: Southern Arizona Bank & Trust Co. (Tucson), joint account. 1926-1940 (Box 169, Folder 3-5)
    - Deposit slips: United Bank & Trust Co. (Tucson), Mrs. A.E.D.'s account. 1939 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Deposit slips: Valley National Bank (Tucson), Mrs. A.E.D.'s account. 1935-1943 (Box 169, Folder 7-8)
    - Deposit slips: Valley National Bank (Tucson), joint account. 1935-1941, 1944 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Deposit slips: Valley National Bank (Tucson). 1936, 1938, 1940-1941, 1948 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate: Speedway & 3rd Ave (rented, includes correspondence regarding rental and furnishings, and shipment of household goods from Flagstaff to Tucson). 1906-1907 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Real Estate: Speedway & Olive Road (photgraphs, lease between J.J. Thornber and G.N. Houston). 1907-1912 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Real Estate: 1189 E. Speedway (photographs, papers regarding purchase from W.A. Cannon, expenses, maintenance, and eventual exchange of property for Charles Turrell's property at 1601 Rincon). 1914-1921 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Real Estate: 1187 E. Speedway (in residence during summers, photographs, blueprints, J.J.Thornber's letter to "The Water Users of Olive Road and Vicinity," and papers relating to Agnes Speese mortage). 1918-1921 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Real Estate: 1601 E. Rincon (photographs, mortgage papers). 1921-1925, 1934-1936 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate: 1230 N. Euclid (papers relating to purchase of Lundberg-Ronstadt property, correspondence with F. Ronstadt). 1929-1930, 1932-1934 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate: 1941 E. 4th St. (papers relating to lease of property from Andrew Lazare). 1930-1932 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Real Estate: 2344 E. Speedway (photographs, lease with W.B. Stevenson). 1936-1943 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Real Estate: 915 E. 5th St. (photographs, papers relating to purchase from James E. Brady, floor plans). 1944-1947 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate: 2120 E. Hampton (floor plans, notes on wiring, sprinkler system, cooler, trees, phone. Catalina Vista Times, vol.5 no.6). 1948-1962 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate: miscellaneous correspondence (includes floor plans on houses considered, business cards of real estate dealers, hotels, apartments, prospect uses of real estate development). 1908-1945 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Real Estate: household furnishings (inventories, insurance policies). (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Real Estate. 1928-1941 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      Includes the following:
      Altadena Heights Addition (1641 E. Broadway, F.R. Benton)
      Blenman Addition (Lots 3-4, Block 8, Carl J. Creamer; 2614 E. Mabel, W.W. Brown; 2911 E. Drachman, L.L. Mcgee; Lots 15-16, Block 23, Lousi Schmid)
      Buell's Addition (1228 E. Lowell Ave, Harry Huston)
      Bruckner's Addition (835 S. Fremont, Preston-Triplett)
      Colonia Solana, Lot 70 (Yocum-Loew)
      Drake's Addition (1400 E. 7th St, Hermes-Love; "Between Vine & Highland, on 9th and 10th," Huff-Roberts-Reinke; 1339 E. Broadway, Stapp-Rudasill)
    - Real Estate: Fairmont Addition (2200 block on 6th St., J.A. Oliver; 2046 E.5th St., M. Alfassa and E. Forman; 2300 Block on 6th St., S.D. Thurston; 428 N. Norton, E.E. Klein; 415 N. Tucson Blvd, A.G. Gerdin; Lot 11, Block 31, Haas-Kitt). 1928-1942 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Real Estate: Feldman Addition. 1918-1937 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      1025 N. 2nd Ave (George Bande)
      418-438 E. Drachman (Corbett-Pyeatt)
      1324 N. 1st Ave (Triplett-Helbig)
      1340 N. 1st Ave (Triplett-Bechtol)
      1339 N. Park Ave (Roger Q. Triplett)
      Lots 1-2, Block 13 (J.C. McQuaid)
      209 E. Helen (Joseph Carlucci)
      1121 N. 2nd Ave (Merton-Ford)
      610-612 E. Helen (Otto L. Dustman)
      608 & 916 E. Helen (Murray-Triplett)
      NW Corner Speedway & Park (Charles C. Wheeler)
      1024 N. Euclid (McCluskey-Granville & Others)
    - Real Estate. 1918-1935 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      Incudes the following:
      Highland Park Addition (7th Ave, between Drachman & Mabel, Corbett-Adamson-Brown)
      Highland re-subdivision of Drake's Addition (1400 Block on 5th St., Frank Mathews)
      Monterey Addition (Section 6, Township 14, Upshaw-burt-Corbett)
      Morning View Addition (Lot 4, Block 9, W.E. Williams)
      New Deal Acres (Lot 1, Block 2, S.P. Christy)
    - Real Estate: Nob Hill Addition. 1920-1936 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      1600 Block on 1st St (Clark-Morton)
      1600 Block on 1st St (Thompson-Young-Morton)
      937 N. Campbell (A.L. Pixley)
      SE Corner of Rincon (Chesney)
      Lots 8-10, Block 9 (Blenman-Leonard)
    - Real Estate. 1919-1943 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      Plumer & Stewart's Addition (1541 E. Mabel, Converse-Jones; 1404 E. Mabel, Helen Buckley)
      Palomar Subdivision: Paseo Grande (Celi-Mirkil)
      Olsen's Addition (Speedway & Olsen, H.M. Hubbard; Lot 7, Block 24, Romine)
      Rieker's Addition (724 E. 10th St., Ziegler)
      Rincon Heights Addition (730 N. Warren Ave, Triplett-Morton-Sellers; 1817 E. 5th St., Roy H. Long; 1700 Block, 4th St., Glover-Rudasill; 1628-1646 E. 4th St;, Gertrude T. Robert; 521 N. Campbell, Crooks-Turner)
    - Real Estate. 1922-1942 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      San Clements (Lots 7-8, block 5, F.H. Maury; Lots 16, block 3, Stockton-Basye; Lot 24, block 4, Stockton-Basye; Lot 7, block 5, Stockton-Basye)
      Speedway Heights Addition (2409 E. 2nd St., Gladys Hayden; 2216 E. Hawthorne, Crawford; 1948 E. Hawthorne, T.A. Gregory)
      Speedway Addition (Fairmount near Dodge, G.E. Russell)
      Speedway-Park Subdivision (Old John Williams House, E.A. Stewart)
      Sunnyside Addition (Block 5, Gandy-Rorabaugh)
      University Extension Addition (Lot 7, Block 4, E.C. Greist)
      University Heights Addition (1149 E. 12th St, Arthur Jacome; 1400 Block on 13th, Black-Pierce)
      University Manor (Lots 4-6, block 5, J.A. Hamilton; 2046 E. 5th St., H.C. Adams)
      Venice Additions (Glenn Avenue Ranch, Clinton Helbig)
    - Real Estate: Tucson City Blocks. 1917-1940 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      Lots 8-9, block 6 (Davis-Romine)
      234 W. 2nd St. (Dorough-Triplett)
      827-835 N. Stone (Johnson-Kirkland-Treis)
      Lot 5, Block 41 (J.B. and C.C. Reidy)
      Lots 10-11, Block 31 (George Parker)
      445 E. 4th St. (Sigma Nu-Miller)
      423 E. 7th St. (Taylor)
      214 N. Jacobus (Wycoff)
      736 S. 3rd Ave (Caid-Triplett)
      510 E. 18th St. (Roos-Elias)